Muhammad Arslan Malik

Web Developer

I am a motivated and analytical Software Engineer with the extensive experience of 3 years in developing Web applications, Core expertise in PHP and JavaScript, I am having great experience with all stages of Software Development Life Cycle including developing, testing and rolling out complex scenarios.



marslanmalik9@gmail.com

+923137899933

H#1, ST#8, Bostan khan road, Chaklala, Scheme 3, Rawalpindi, Pakistan

React Js

Github

JavaScript / Jquery

01 March, 1996

Restful Api

HTML5 / CSS

Jira

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Qisstpay

05/2021 - Present

Islamabad

Software Engineer Dev5

01/2019 - 05/2021

Islamahad

PORTFOLIO

Qisstpay

Qisstpay offers Buy Now, Pay Later Services across Pakistan with Interest-Free Installments to Debit & Credit Card Users. All of this to let GenZ & Millennials to not stop shopping!

Common Waste & Dumpster Rental

 Common Waste is a waste consultant specializing in customized dumpster rental for roll off dumpsters.

R&R

R&R is your one stop shop for finding and booking one of our reliable R&R Cleaning Pros. From our platform you can find and book an R&R Cleaning Pro in a matter of minutes. Never feel bogged down by endless hours spent on turning over your rentals again! With our simple system and vetting process, you can rest assured that you will receive fast and reliable service for your rentals, so that you can get back to maintaining quality customer service, maximizing your bookings, and spending time with your loved ones!

Global Ocean Center

- (Shop Ocean) Our marketplace makes it easy to find the best products and services to support any oceanic venture.
- (Talk Ocean) Our dynamic platform designed to help anyone drive oceanfocused projects forward.

Domain Esports

 Domain Esports provides free and paid software to help players and streamers reach their best, whether you need to find a team or find a player replacement, or if you are turning your hobby into a profession and need your own branded website with an integrated accounting system, Domain Esports is there to help you.

Ignyte

Ignyte is a web application with multiple modules, core functionality is social platform like facebook (posts, likes, comments, shares, friends etc), Chat, Tournaments, Teams are also part of this Application.

EDUCATION

BS (Computer Science) PMAS Arid University Rawalpindi

Slack

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Laravel

Bootstrap

PERSONALITY

Organized

MySql

Yii2

Creativity

Communicative

Punctuality

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative Teamwork

Communication

Decision Making

Leadership

Positive Attitude

03/2014 - 03/2018 3.34 (CGPA)